

STIFFY NAVALES

APPLICATION SYSTEMS ENGR.

- 0935 7632 195
- stiffy.navales@icloud.com

- Bukluran 2 Silang Cavite Philippines
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/stiffynavales-b10555179/

Has been working for almost 6 years in IT industry. Has an experience on different field of IT - Network Admin/Data Analyst/Software Development/Server Administration/ and currently working on Web Designing- specializing in Figma & Webflow.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Application Systems Engineer FUJITSU GLOBAL DELIVERY CENTER

March 2022- Present

- Design, develop, and implement software applications and systems.
- Create and maintain technical documentation for applications and systems.

Technical Support Engineer Technofreeze Inc./INLAND Warehousing

July 2018 - September 2021

- Troubleshoots an organization's software, hardware, and IT systems.
- Collaborating with other support engineers to share knowledge and improve the support process.

Information Technology Specialist AgileTouch Data Outsourcing PH

December 2015 - March 2016

- Install, configure, and maintain computer systems, servers, and network devices.
- Ensure software licenses are up-to-date and compliant with vendor agreements.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

- Bachelor of Science in Information Technology
 University of Perpetual Help JONELTA
 2012 2015
- Bachelor of Science in Information Technology
 Lyceum of the Philippines University-Cavite
 2011 2012

RELEVANT SKILLS

- Data Science(Palantir)
- Python Automation/Web Development(Django)
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Web Designing(Figma, Webflow)
- CRM's(Wordpress-Elementor, Shopify)
- Database and SQL(MySQL, PHP)
- Photo and video editing(Photoshop, Premiere Pro)
- · Adaptability and continuous learning

CHARACTER REFERENCE

Mark Ariel Tolentino
Fuiitsu

Sr. Application Systems Engineer/Consultant 09669401601

- Julius Bagasona Grand Alphatech International company IT Administrator 09267371963
- ▲ Jean Claude Uriarte
 Personiv

 Associate Process M

Associate Process Manager 09394158349